{
    "id": "6812cf1cdf94481d8b0dc9127a7c0347",
    "title": "Prepositions exercise for kids",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5f21b87ada014fc8864ff53378a3309e",
            "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The boy ran …………………………….. the street.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "across",
                        "on",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He walked ………………………….. the building.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "around",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The train goes ……………………….. a tunnel.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "through",
                        "along"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I walked …………………………….. the river bank.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "along"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is standing …………………………. the gate?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Your glasses are ………………………….. your nose.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "over",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The cat is hiding ………………………….. the door.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "behind",
                        "below",
                        "under"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Come and stand ………………………….. me, Jane.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "in front of",
                        "across"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dog came running …………………………… its master, wagging its tail.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "to",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They walked …………………………………. each other.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "for",
                        "towards"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}